John J. Sirica Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States District Court File, 1952-1986 (Box 12-105)
  - Case File, 1952-1986 (Box 15-90)
    - Other cases (Box 54)
      - Electrical equipment litigation (Box 55)
        - Cases (Box 56)
          - City of Burlington v. Westinghouse Elec. Corp.
            - Evidence
              - Cost, 1964
            - Form of verdict, 1964
            - General, 1963-1964, undated
            - Interrogatories (Box 57)
              - First set
                - Defendants to plaintiffs, 1964, (2 folders)
                - Plaintiffs to defendants, 1964, (2 folders)
              - Second set, 1964
            - Jury
              - Instructions
                - Final, 1964
                - Prayers for relief, 1964 (Box 58)
                - Specific issues, 1964
              - Introductory remarks, 1964
              - Voir dire proceedings, 1964
            - Motions
              - Consolidation of cases, 1963-1964
              - Directed verdict and mistrial, 1964
              - Subpoena duces tecum, 1964-1966, undated, (3 folders)
            - Opinion, 1963
            - Post-trial documents, 1965, (2 folders) (Box 59)
            - Power transformer and second priority products, 1964-1965, (3 folders)
            - Pretrial conference, 1962
            - Stipulations and agreements, 1964
            - Testimony for the grand jury and Estes Kefauver Committee, 1964, undated
            - Witnesses, 1964
          - Other (Box 60)
            - Aluminum cable cases
              - General, 1965-1967, undated, (4 folders)
              - Pretrial orders, 1966
              - Transcripts, 1965-1966, undated, (2 folders)
            - Answers to complaint
              - 1963-1965
              - Undated (Box 61)
            - Attorneys, 1962
            - Correspondence, 1962-1965, (2 folders)
            - Defendants
              - Peripheral, 1963
              - Summary of pending cases in nonpriority product lines, 1965, (2 folders)
            - Fraudulent concealment, 1962-1963, undated, (2 folders)
            - General, 1952, 1962-1966, undated, (7 folders) (Box 62)
            - Interrogatories
              - Answers by plaintiffs and defendants
                - 1964
                - 1965 (Box 63)
              - General, 1965
              - Objections, 1965
              - Priority product line, 1963
            - Motions to dismiss, 1964-1966
            - Orders
              - General, 1962-1964
              - Pretrial
                - Local
                - Briefs and motions, 1964
                - General, 1964-1965
                - National
                - Notebook, 1962-1965, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 64)
                - Working papers, 1963, undated, (4 folders)
            - Press, 1964, 1973, undated (Box 65)
            - Production of documents
              - General, 1965
              - National rule 34, 1963-1964
            - Rulings
              - General, 1962-1966, (3 folders)
              - Statute of limitations, 1962-1963, (2 folders)
            - Settlement program, 1962-1964
            - Transfer of cases under Title 28, United States Code, 1404a, 1965-1966, undated, (3 folders) (Box 66)
        - Co-ordinating Committee for Multiple Litigation of the United States District Courts
          - Antitrust Conference, Philadelphia, Pa., 1962
          - General
            - 1962-1964, (3 folders)
            - 1965-1973, undated, (8 folders) (Box 67)
          - Meetings
            - 1963
              - Feb.-May, (2 folders)
              - Nov., (3 folders) (Box 68)
            - 1964, (3 folders)
            - 1965, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 69)
          - Orders, pretrial
            - General, 1962
            - Proposed, 1962-1963, (2 folders)
            - Southern District of New York cases, 1962
      - Environmental Defense Fund v. Adams, 1977
      - Environmental Tectonics Corp. v. Robinson, 1975
      - Fairchild & Co. v. Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac R.R., 1981
      - Fensterwald v. United States Cent. Intelligence Agency, 1977
      - Ficara v. Watson, 1959
      - First Am. Bank v. United Equity Corp., 1981
      - First Nat'l Bank & Trust Co. v. American Sec. & Trust Co., 1977
      - Foster v. Bork, 1977
      - Foundation on Economic Trends v. Heckler, 1984-1986 (Box 70)
      - Frederick v. Metropolitan Life Ins. Co., 1957
      - Fulwood v. Clemmer, 1962
      - Gertler v. Employers' Fire Ins. Co., 1961
      - Godbold v. Overholser, 1962
      - Golin v. Physicians Int'l Press, 1970
      - Graham v. Clusen, 1977
      - Green v. Silver, 1962
      - Grunstein v. Baylor, 1961
      - Guaranty Sav. & Loan Ass'n v. Federal Home Loan Bank Bd., 1971
      - Guidace v. Young, 1957
      - Hadigan v. Board of Governors, 1978
      - Hamburger v. Wormley, 1957
      - Hankins v. Kane, 1967, undated
      - Harper v. Blumenthal, 1979
      - Harper v. Miller, 1980
      - Harshaw v. Pan Am. World Airways, 1975
      - Hatch v. Riggs Nat'l Bank, 1968
      - Hayes v. RCA Serv. Co., 1982
      - Health Research Group v. Kennedy, 1978-1979
      - Hill, Christopher & Phillips, P. C. v. United States Postal Serv., 1982
      - Horne v. Francis I. DuPont & Co., 1977
      - Human Resources Management v. Weaver, 1977-1978
      - Illinois Scientific Devs. v. Honeywell, Inc., 1967
      - Information Acquisition Corp. v. Department of Justice, 1978
      - International Ass'n of Machinists v. National Ry. Labor Conference, 1970
      - Jones v. District of Columbia, 1977
      - Joyner v. Joyner, 1957
      - Kaycee, Inc. v. Simonson, 1966
      - Kennedy v. Jones, 1975-1976
      - Keough v. Pearson, 1964
      - Knight v. Hersh, 1961
      - Kopan v. George Washington Univ., 1975
      - Kropf v. Anacostia Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n, 1957
      - Landsberger v. Freeman, 1963
      - Lapin v. Mathews, 1976
      - Lapsley v. American Inst. of Certified Public Accountants, 1965
      - Latham v. District of Columbia Transit Sys., 1963
      - Lee v. England, 1962
      - Lighthall v. Watson, 1959
      - Lillycrop v. Kresge, 1961
      - Littell v. Udall, 1964-1965
      - Local Union 13410, United Mine Workers v. United Mine Workers, 1971-1975
      - Lombardo v. Handler, 1975
      - Lumbermens Mut. Casualty Co. v. A-T-O, Inc., 1977
      - Madison v. Lee, 1975
      - Majestic Builders Corp. v. Mount Airy Baptist Church Housing Corp., 1977
      - Mardirosian v. American Inst. of Architects, 1979
      - Marimont v. Mathews, 1976
      - Mason v. Claytor, 1978
      - Mayhew v. Mabro Constr., 1974
      - Mazaleski v. Treusdell, 1975
      - McCarthy v. Cahill, 1965-1966
      - McMullen v. Warner, 1976
      - Mervin v. Bonfanti, 1976
      - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, Inc. v. Byrd, 1968, (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Misko v. United States, 1978
      - Mobil Oil Corp. v. Dann, 1976-1978
      - Morgan v. District of Columbia, 1982
      - Motion Picture Studio Mechanics Local 22 v. Columbia Broadcasting Sys., 1977
      - Mutual Broadcasting Sys. v. International Bhd. of Elec. Workers Local 1200, 1975
      - National Council on the Facts of Overpopulation v. Gaplin, 1963
      - National Motor Freight Traffic Ass'n v. United States, 1967
      - National Resources Defense Council v. Coleman, 1975
      - Nederostek v. Adams, 1978
      - Neely v. Blumenthal, 1978
      - Neely v. Simon, 1977
      - O'Bryant v. Dunlop, 1976
      - Oerlemans v. National Broadcasting Co., 1962
      - Old Kent Bank & Trust Co. v. Martin, 1959
      - Outdoor Power Equip. Inst. v. Environmental Protection Agency, 1977
      - Outlaw v. Goodwin, 1961
      - Owens v. Brown, 1978
      - Parking Management, Inc. v. Union Center Plaza Assocs., 1976
      - Payne v. Howard, 1977
      - Perillo v. Washington Hosp. Center, 1967
      - Pharmaceutical Mfrs. Ass'n v. Weinberger, 1975
      - Pinkney v. District of Columbia, 1977
      - Rammamuri v. Rolls-Royce, Ltd., 1978
      - Rendleman v. Ladd, 1961
      - Rhodes v. Elwood, 1961
      - Rice v. Royall, 1959
      - Richards v. Columbia Broadcasting Sys., 1958
      - Riss & Co. v. Association of Am. R.R.
        - Allowance of costs and amending the judgment, 1960-1962, undated
        - Appellate court documents
          - Association of W. Rys. v. Riss & Co.
            - 1961, (2 folders); (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box 72, Box 73, Box 74)
            - 1962
          - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Ry. v. Riss & Co., 1959-1960
          - Atlantic Coast Line R.R. v. Riss & Co.
            - 1958, (2 folders)
            - 1959-1960, (2 folders) (Box 75)
        - Attorneys' fees, 1961-1964, undated
        - Background information
          - Eastern R.R. Presidents Conference v. Noerr Motor Freight, Inc., 1957-1961, (4 folders)
          - General, 1954-1963, undated, (2 folders)
        - Card file, undated (Box 76-77)
        - Complaint, 1958-1959, undated (Box 78)
        - Counterclaims
          - Anititrust
            - 1959-1960, (5 folders)
          - Common law, 1960
        - Correspondence, 1957-1963, (2 folders) (Box 79)
        - Damages, 1958-1960
        - Digests of
          - Depositions, 1954-1955, (3 folders)
          - Legal memoranda, undated
        - Evidence
          - Admissibility of, 1960, undated
          - General, 1960, undated
          - Rates, 1960 (Box 80)
        - Exhibits
          - General, 1960, undated
          - Objections to plaintiff's, 1960, undated, (2 folders)
        - Form of verdict, 1960, undated
        - General
          - 1955-1962, (5 folders)
          - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 81)
        - Indexes of
          - Transcripts, depositions, and pleadings, undated
          - Trial record, undated
        - Interrogatories
          - 1955-1958
          - 1959, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 82)
          - 1960
        - Issues of fact and law, 1959, undated
        - Jury
          - Instructions
            - Defendants' recommendations, 1960, (2 folders)
            - Final
              - 1960, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 83)
              - Undated
            - Preliminary
              - Background information, 1955-1959, undated
              - General, 1960, undated
            - Special, 1960, undated
          - Voir dire proceedings, 1959-1960, undated
        - Motions re
          - Directed verdict, 1960, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 84)
          - Suspension of proceedings, 1958-1959, undated
        - Opinions and memoranda by Sirica, 1958-1962
        - Orders, 1958-1960, undated
        - Plaintiff's conspiracy proof against defendants, 1960
        - Pleadings
          - General
            - 1954, (2 folders) (Box 85)
            - 1955-1960, undated, (4 folders)
          - Index, undated
        - Pretrial
          - Conferences, 1959, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 86)
          - General, 1958-1960, undated
        - Request for admission of genuineness of documents, 1958-1960
        - Statute of limitations, 1960, undated
        - Stipulations
          - General, 1959-1960, undated
          - Proposed, 1959, undated, (3 folders)
        - Transcripts (Box 87)
          - Charges for, 1958-1960
          - Hearing on motions, 1959, (2 folders)
        - Witnesses
          - Availability, 1960, undated
          - Rule re missing witnesses, 1960, undated
      - Riverside Gen. Hosp. v. Schweiker, 1982
      - Roemer v. Hoffman, 1976
      - Rose v. Hakim, 1971
      - Sachs v. Plumbers Local 5, 1969
      - Schliep v. Demaras, 1976
      - Schmidt v. Interstate Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n, 1976-1977
      - Schoenman v. Secretary of State, 1967
      - Schreiber v. W. E. Hutton & Co., 1974
      - Scott v. Weinberger, 1976
      - Seneca Indians v. Brucker, 1957
      - Sherman v. Thompson, 1959
      - Smaldone v. Kurtz, 1978
      - Smiertka v. United States Dep't of Treasury, 1978
      - St. Lawrence v. United States, 1977
      - Steuart Petroleum Co. v. United States, 1977
      - Texaco, Inc. v. Udall, 1969
      - Tewalt v. Tewalt, 1960
      - Thomas v. United Mine Workers, 1976-1977
      - Town of East Hartford v. Harris, 1978
      - Troublefield v. United States, 1966
      - United States v. Alston, 1980
      - United States v. Ammidown For additional material see Container 19, Bench Book
        - General, 1971-1980, undated, (2 folders)
        - Jury, 1972 (Box 88)
        - Press, 1972
        - Second degree murder plea, 1972
        - Sentencing, 1958-1960, 1971-1972, undated
        - Suppression hearing, 1971-1972, undated
      - United States v. Artis, 1970
      - United States v. Baker, undated
      - United States v. Blackshear, 1958-1963
      - United States v. Bowman, 1966
      - United States v. Brewster, 1957
      - United States v. Bristol Myers For additional material see Container 19, Bench Book
      - United States v. Brooker, 1962
      - United States v. Daniels, 1969
      - United States v. Dougherty, 1971
      - United States v. Enten, 1970-1975, undated, (3 folders) (Box 89)
      - United States v. Fletcher, 1971
      - United States v. Frazier, 1981, undated
      - United States v. Green, 1961
      - United States v. Hanrahan, 1963-1966
      - United States v. Hart, 1974
      - United States v. Hodges, 1957
      - United States v. Isaac, 1969
      - United States v. Izlar, 1968
      - United States v. Joyner, 1967
      - United States v. Lee
        - General, 1971-1974, undated, (3 folders)
        - Reduction of sentence, 1972 (Box 90)
        - Rule on evidence re post conspiracy declarations, 1972
      - United States v. Lemonakis See United States v. Enten
      - United States v. Lot 800, Square 1928, District of Columbia, 1959
      - United States v. Mann, 1962
      - United States v. McIlwain, 1977
      - United States v. Misenheimer, 1961
      - United States v. Moore, 1971
      - United States v. Myles, 1977
      - United States v. Ross, 1966
      - United States v. Schurman, 1965
      - United States v. Suggs, 1967
      - United States v. Ward, 1971, undated
      - United States v. Washington, Va. & Md. Coach Co., 1967
      - United States v. Wilkes, 1968
      - United States v. Williams, 1963
      - Vogel v. Tenneco Oil Co., 1967
      - Wager v. Pro, 1975
      - Walter Holm & Co. v. Hardin, 1970
      - Watkins v. Wilson, 1977
      - Watson v. Defelice, 1977
      - In re Wheat Farmers Antitrust Class Action, 1977
      - Windsor v. State Farm Ins. Co., 1981
      - Wixom v. Bell, 1979
      - Yakoumatos v. District of Columbia Transit Sys., 1967
      - Young v. Netherlands Owners, Inc., 1969
      - Zoslow v. West, 1959
  - Bench Books, 1957-1983, For additional material see Containers 19, 26, and 56, same heading (Box 90-95)
    Bound volumes containing Sirica's notes about cases that came before his court.
    Arranged chronologically.
    - 1957-1958, (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - 1958-1959, (4 folders) (Box 91)
    - 1960-1965, (4 folders) (Box 92)
    - 1965-1967, (3 folders) (Box 93)
    - 1967-1972, (3 folders) (Box 94)
    - 1977-1983 (Box 95)
  - Office File, 1954-1986 (Box 95-105)
    Correspondence, memoranda, background information, invitations, jury instructions, notes, and printed matter.
    Arranged alphabetically by name of person or organization, subject, or type of material.
    - Awards and honors (Box 95)
      - Bust of Sirica presented to Georgetown University Law Center, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1982-1984
      - General, 1963, 1970-1981
      - Lido Civic Club testimonial dinner, Washington, D.C., 1978-1979
      - National Father of the Year, 1978-1979
      - National Italian American Foundation bicentennial tribute dinner, 1976-1977
      - Tom C. Clark Award, 1985-1986
      - University of Detroit, Detroit, Mich., President's Cabinet Award, 1979-1980
    - Boehm, Frederick L., 1977-1979 (Box 96)
    - Federal rules of criminal procedure, rule 50(b), 1972-1973, undated
    - Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.
      - Alumni Association, 1975-1985
      - Board of Regents, 1979-1986
      - General, 1971-1985
      - Moot court, 1966-1975, undated
      - Seminar on advocacy, 1982
    - Grand juries, undated
    - Immunity, 1969-1971, undated (Box 97)
    - Investiture ceremonies, 1967-1972, undated
    - Invitations accepted
      - 1966-1975, (5 folders)
      - 1976-1979, (6 folders) (Box 98)
      - 1980-1982, (3 folders) (Box 99)
    - John J. Sirica Portrait Trust Fund, 1976-1978
    - Judicial
      - Appointment, ceremony, 1957
      - Ethics
        - Financial disclosure
          - General
            - 1969-1975, (2 folders)
            - 1976-1978 (Box 100)
          - Honoraria, 1974-1976, (2 folders)
          - Reports, 1975-1984, (2 folders)
        - General, undated
    - Jury instructions
      - B-M, 1961-1967, undated
      - N-S, 1954-1966 (Box 101)
      - United States v.
        - An-Hu, 1957-1968, (5 folders)
        - Ja-Wo, 1957-1968, undated, (5 folders) (Box 102)
      - Unidentified, undated
    - Justinian Society of Lawyers, 1967-1973
    - Kronheim, Milton S., 1960, 1973-1979, undated
    - Law clerks
      - Attori, Mark D., 1983-1985
      - Christofferson, Todd, 1971-1973
      - General, 1971-1986, (2 folders) (Box 103)
      - Memoranda, 1978-1980, undated
    - Lorton Youth Center, Lorton, Va., 1970-1971, undated, (2 folders)
    - Magistrates, 1971
    - Media and Law Conference, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, Tenn., 1977-1978
    - Memorial proceedings, 1960-1978, undated
    - National Italian American Foundation, 1977-1986
    - Naturalization proceedings, 1962, 1975, undated (Box 104)
    - No Greater Love, Washington, D.C., 1977-1985, undated
    - Phi Alpha Delta Law Fraternity, 1966-1983
    - Pratt, John H., 1973
    - Press, 1957-1986, undated, (5 folders)
    - Schwabacher, Judy, 1979-1982
    - Scripps-Howard Foundation Awards panel, 1977-1981
    - Senior judge
      - Statistics
        - 1977-1979
        - 1980-1985, (3 folders) (Box 105)
      - Status, 1977-1986, (2 folders)
    - United States District Court for the District of Columbia, 1962-1975, undated
    - Winchell, Walter, 1977-1978
- Speeches and Writings File, 1949-1986 (Box 106-117)
  Correspondence, memoranda, speeches, research material, book drafts, book reviews, articles, notes, financial and legal papers, and printed matter relating chiefly to Sirica's post-Watergate speeches and writings.
  Filed in two categories: speeches that are arranged chronologically and writings arranged alphabetically.
  - Speeches (Box 106)
    - By Sirica
      - 1958-1974, (6 folders)
      - 1975
        - Apr.-Aug., (4 folders)
        - Sept.-Nov., (4 folders) (Box 107)
      - 1976-1977, (7 folders)
      - 1978-1981, undated, (5 folders) (Box 108)
    - By others, 1973-1981, undated
    - Correspondence
      - 1975
        - Jan.-July, (2 folders)
        - Aug.-Nov. (Box 109)
      - 1976-1977
    - Miscellaneous, 1958, 1975-1976, undated
    - Press, 1973-1982, undated
    - Research material
      - 1949-1973, (4 folders)
      - 1974-1984, undated, (3 folders) (Box 110)
    - Washington Speakers Bureau, Alexandria, Va., 1982-1983
  - Writings
    - By Sirica
      - "After the Dam Broke," New York Times, 24 Apr. 1979
      - Autobiography, 1975, undated
      - To Set the Record Straight: The Break-in, the Tapes, the Conspirators, the Pardon (1979)
        - Book Digest Magazine, undated
        - Correspondence
          - 1976-1978
          - 1979-1980, (11 folders) (Box 111)
          - 1981-1984 (Box 112)
        - Doubleday & Co., 1977-1978
        - Drafts, undated
          - A, (3 folders)
          - B, (2 folders) (Box 113)
          - C, (4 folders)
          - Notes, 1978, undated (Box 114)
        - Harper & Row Publishers, 1976-1977
        - Look magazine serialization, 1979-1980
        - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978, undated
        - Movie For additional material see Container 51, Liddy, G. Gordon
          - 1979-1980, (4 folders)
          - 1981-1983, undated, (3 folders) (Box 115)
        - New American Library, 1979-1980
        - Press, 1979-1980, undated
        - Reviews, 1979-1980, undated
        - Stacks, John, notes from interviews, 1978
        - Stans, Maurice, 1979
        - Sterling Lord Agency, Inc., 1977-1983, undated, (3 folders) (Box 116)
        - W. W. Norton & Co. For additional material see Container 51, Liddy, G. Gordon
          - Contracts
            - General, 1977-1980, undated
            - Indemnity clause, 1977
          - Financial papers, 1978-1982
          - General, 1978-1984, (2 folders)
      - "Unforgettable Jack Dempsey," Readers Digest, Mar. 1986 See also Container 118, Dempsey, Jack (Box 117)
    - By others, 1973, undated
    - Unidentified, undated
- Miscellany, 1932-1985 (Box 117-123)
  Correspondence, memoranda, case files, family papers, financial and legal papers, background information, and printed matter relating primarily to Sirica's early career as a lawyer.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person, topic, or type of material.
  - Assistant United States Attorney for the District of Columbia, reference notebooks, undated, (3 folders) (Box 117)
  - Biographical file, 1967-1985, undated, (2 folders)
  - Dempsey, Jack See also Container 117, "Unforgettable Jack Dempsey" (Box 118)
    - General, 1953-1984, undated, (5 folders)
    - Television program proposal, undated
  - Family papers, 1966-1977, undated, (3 folders)
  - Financial and legal papers
    - General, 1962-1984, (2 folders)
    - Personal injury claim, 1961-1963, undated, (5 folders) (Box 119)
  - General counsel, House Select Committee to Investigate the Federal Communications Commission, Flamm v. Noble
    - Appellate court documents
      - 1944-1946, (2 folders)
      - 1949, (2 folders) (Box 120, Box 121)
    - General, 1943-1949, 1977, undated
    - Notebooks, 1932-1966, (2 folders)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977, undated (Box 122)
  - Press, 1956, 1982-1984, undated
  - Private legal practice
    - Cases
      - Day v. Smith's Transfer & Storage Co., 1949-1953, undated
      - Jaeck v. Thaw, 1937, undated
      - Liberty Mut. Ins. Co. v. Capital Excavating Co., 1951, undated
      - MacMillan v. Knost, undated
      - McLaughlin v. Hecht Co., 1950-1954, undated, (2 folders)
      - Peterson v. Capital Transit Co., 1950-1951
      - Sommerville v. Capital Transit Co., 1949-1951
      - United States v. Cullum, 1950-1953, undated (Box 123)
      - Young v. Mount, 1949-1952, undated
    - General, 1952-1954, undated
    - Legal memoranda, 1947-1952, undated
    - Pleadings, 1949-1955, undated, (2 folders)
    - Press, undated
  - Wolfson, Louis E., 1966-1969, undated, (2 folders)
- 2021 Addition, 1973-1978 (Box 124-125)
  Diaries containing daily entries and general observations, largely relating to the Watergate Affair. Topics covered include court proceedings, jury selection, planning for deposition of President Richard M. Nixon, sentencing, autobiography drafts and notes, meetings and events, and Nixon's televised interview with David Frost. Also included is a lightly annotated copy of Nixon's memoir.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Diaries, 1973, Oct. (Box 124)
  - Diaries, 1974, Jun.- 1974, Sept.
  - Diaries, 1974, Oct.
  - Diaries, 1974, Nov.-1975, Apr. 20
  - Diaries, 1975, Apr. 30-1978, Feb. 9
  - RN: The Memoirs of Richard Nixon, 1978
  - RN: The Memoirs of Richard Nixon, 1978 (Box 125)
- Classified, 1973 (Box CL 1)
  Government classified documents containing sensitive security information.
  Correspondence, memoranda, and transcripts organized and described according to the series, boxes, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - United States District Court File (Box CL 1)
    - Case File
      - Watergate cases
        - Cases